{
    "subject": "resource/Black_'n_Blue",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The hometown of Black 'n Blue is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9366751909255981,
            "question": "What is the hometown of Black 'n Blue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6358704566955566,
            "question": "Is Black 'n Blue a band from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5849359035491943,
            "question": "Where are Black 'n Blue originally from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5604495406150818,
            "question": "Where was Black 'n Blue formed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5151360630989075,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Black 'n Blue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4833069443702698,
            "question": "Is Black 'n Blue an American band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4599964916706085,
            "question": "Black 'n Blue hails from which location?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4584948420524597,
            "question": "What country is Black 'n Blue from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3845460116863251,
            "question": "Can you name the home nation of Black 'n Blue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18244780600070953,
            "question": "Which country considers Black 'n Blue as one of their own musical acts?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The hometown of Black 'n Blue is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8896_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name the home nation of Black 'n Blue?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8896_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Black 'n Blue from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8896_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Black 'n Blue hails from which location?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8896_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8896_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8896_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8896_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8896_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8896_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8896_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8896_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8896_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8896_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8896_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about the band Black 'N' Blue, which was formed in Portland, OR, and has members who are U.S. citizens or residents. Therefore, it can be inferred that the hometown of Black 'n Blue is the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several passages state Black N' Blue was formed in Portland, Oregon.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}